(mediative music)
♪ I wanna be with you,
gotta be with you ♪
♪ Need to be with you ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I wanna be with you,
gotta be with you ♪
♪ Need to be with you ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Chemistry was crazy
from the get-go ♪
♪ Neither one of us knew why ♪
♪ We didn't build
nothing overnight ♪
♪ 'Cause a love like
this takes some time ♪
♪ People swore it
off as a phase ♪
♪ Said we can't see that ♪
♪ Now from top to bottom ♪
♪ They see that
we did that, yes ♪
♪ It's so true that, yes ♪
♪ We've been through it, yes ♪
♪ We got real, yes ♪
♪ See baby we been ♪
♪ Too strong for too long, and
I can't be without you, baby ♪
♪ And I'll be waiting
up until you get home ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't sleep
without you, baby ♪
♪ Anybody who's ever loved,
ya know just what I feel ♪
♪ Too hard to fake it,
nothing can replace it ♪
♪ Call the radio if you just
can't be without your baby ♪
♪ I got a question for ya ♪
♪ See I already
know the answer ♪
♪ But still I wanna ask you ♪
♪ Would you lie, no ♪
♪ Make me cry, no ♪
♪ Do somethin' behind my back
and then try to cover it up ♪
♪ Well, neither would I, baby ♪
♪ My love is only
your love, yes ♪
♪ I'll be faithful, yes ♪
♪ I'm for real, yes ♪
♪ And with us you'll
always know the deal ♪
♪ We've been too
strong for too long ♪
♪ And I can't be
without you, baby ♪
♪ And I'll be waiting
up until you get home ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't sleep
without you, baby ♪
♪ Anybody who's ever loved,
ya know just what I feel ♪
♪ Too hard to fake it,
nothing can replace it ♪
♪ Call the radio if you just
can't be without your baby ♪
♪ See this is real talk ♪
♪ I'm always stay,
no matter what ♪
♪ Good or bad, thick and thin ♪
♪ Right or wrong,
all day everyday ♪
♪ Now if you're down on
love or don't believe ♪
♪ This ain't for you,
no, this ain't for you ♪
♪ And if you got it
deep in your heart ♪
♪ And deep down you
know that it's true ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Well, let me see you put
your hands up, hands up ♪
♪ Fellas tell your
lady she's the one ♪
♪ Fellas tell your lady
she's the one, oh ♪
♪ Put your hands up, hands up ♪
♪ Ladies let him know
he's got your love ♪
♪ Look him right in
his eyes and tell him ♪
♪ We've been too
strong for too long ♪
♪ And I can't be
without you, baby ♪
♪ I'll be waiting up
until you get home ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't sleep
without you, baby ♪
♪ Anybody who's ever loved,
ya know just what I feel ♪
♪ Too hard to fake it,
nothing can replace it ♪
♪ Call the radio if you just
can't be without your baby ♪
♪ Hey, oh ♪
♪ I wanna be with you,
gotta be with you ♪
♪ Need to be with you ♪
♪ I wanna be with you,
gotta be with you ♪
♪ Need to be with you ♪
♪ I wanna be with you,
gotta be with you ♪
♪ Need to be with you ♪